Alexandra R. Kauffman

Los Angeles, California
(805) 630-2054 — arkauffma@gmail.com
github.com/arkauffman
linkedin.com/in/alexandrakauffman
alexandrakauffman.com

Education

Bachelor of Arts May 2017

University of Wisconsin-Madison

Major: Communication Arts; Certificate: Computer Science

Summary

I am a web developer and have worked with many programming languages, including HTML, CSS, Java, JavaScript, jQuery, Ruby on Rails, and Node.js. Prior to being a web developer, I was a student at the University of Wisconsin-Madison where I earned a degree in Communication Arts and a certificate in Computer Science. Within the many Computer Science courses I took at UW-Madison, I learned the art of pseudocode, the value in debugging, and the theory behind Computer Science.

Skills

- JavaScript
- Java
- HTML
- CSS
- jQuery
- Ruby
- · Ruby on Rails
- React

- Node.js
- Mongoose
- Express
- Git/GitHub
- Bash
- RESTful programming
- External APIs

Experience

Student

General Assembly | Los Angeles, CA

June 2017- September 2017

August 2014-May 2017

Owner

Nails By Alex | Madison, WI

o Built a home-based manicure business at the University of Wisconsin-Madison based on social media and referrals. Managed a personal website in which clients made appointments. Dealt with public relations, revenue management, promotional writing, and several social media platforms.

SEO Consultant

July 2016-October 2016

The Soap Opera | Madison, WI

Organized and uploaded content on the Soap Opera's website. Photographed and uploaded images corresponding to a product's name. Checked inventory and updated the website according to whether or not an item was in stock. Formatted error pages to help guide users back to a page that is available.

Brand Representative

May 2016-July 2017

Uber | Madison, WI

Engaged with the community to promote Uber's services. Distributed marketing materials.
 Communicated brand talking points. Helped riders with technology and product by demonstration.

Marketing Intern

May 2016-September 2016

IH Concepts | Madison, WI

o Managed social media pages, including Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter, and IH Concept's blog. Increased Facebook page's interaction, and wrote blog posts and edited/designed new content.